<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="com.jonnyzzz.mcp-steroid" url="https://github.com/jonnyzzz/mcp-steroid/releases/download/0.90.0/mcp-steroid-0.90.0-64b20612.zip" version="0.90.0-64b20612">
    <idea-version since-build="253"/>
    <name>MCP Steroid</name>
    <vendor>jonnyzzz.com</vendor>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><b>MCP Steroid</b> brings the full power of the IntelliJ Platform to AI agents through the Model Context Protocol (MCP).</p>
<p>IntelliJ platform works for AI agents as great as for human developers.</p>
<ul>
<li><b>9 MCP Tools:</b> Control IntelliJ IDEA programmatically — execute code, take screenshots, discover actions, debug, and more</li>
<li><b>58 MCP Resources:</b> Comprehensive guides covering LSP, IDE operations, debugger, tests, VCS, and more</li>
<li><b>Vision Capabilities:</b> AI agents can see your IDE with screenshots and OCR</li>
<li><b>Deep Integration:</b> Access PSI, inspections, refactorings, and full IntelliJ Platform API</li>
<li><b>Human Oversight:</b> Review and approve code execution with configurable safety controls</li>
</ul>
<p>Compatible with all IntelliJ Platform-based IDEs: IntelliJ IDEA, PyCharm, WebStorm, GoLand, CLion, Rider, and more.</p>
<p>Requirements: IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 or newer (build 253 or later).</p>
<p>Visit <a href="https://mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com">mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com</a> for documentation and examples.</p>]]></description>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[<h2>What's New in v0.90.0</h2>
<h3>ClaudeCode debugs an application in Rider -- MCP Steroid</h3>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/g73vZCO-YRw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>In this video, ClaudeCode drives Rider debugger workflows through MCP Steroid, including breakpoint setup, debugger control, and IDE-driven test execution.</p>
<h3>DPAIA Arena: First Success Metrics</h3>
<p>As of 2026-03-02, the first completed A/B comparison set shows:</p>
<li>Fix rate: `4/4` with MCP Steroid and `4/4` without MCP.</li>
<li>Average agent time: `412s` with MCP vs `526s` without MCP.</li>
<li>Net speedup: MCP was `22%` faster on average (`114s` gain per case).</li>
<li>Cost: MCP was about `10%` cheaper across our 4-test experiment set.</li>
<li>Strongest gains were on complex multi-file tasks (`21-27%` faster), while simple search-and-replace tasks were effectively neutral.</li>
<h3>Prompt Platform Rework</h3>
<li>Added a dedicated `prompts-api` module (`ArticlePart`, `IdeFilter`, `PromptsContext`) and reworked generation around article parts with computed filters.</li>
<li>Migrated prompt articles to the single-article model with line-2 filters and fence annotations, including multi-IDE filter support.</li>
<li>Replaced SkillCatalog YAML frontmatter with article properties and removed obsolete filter code paths.</li>
<li>Moved prompt quality gates into the prompts pipeline (`KtBlock` compilation and debugger prompt quality coverage).</li>
<h3>Additional Validations</h3>
<li>Added article quality contract tests and stricter prompt content checks.</li>
<li>Updated prompt examples to compilable fences and replaced deprecated IntelliJ 2025.3 API usages.</li>
<li>Included kotlinc version in `KtBlock` compilation cache keys to prevent stale cache reuse across compiler upgrades.</li>
<li>Hardened release/update validation by using actual GitHub release asset URLs for `updatePlugins.xml`, failing fast on missing `VERSION`/release URL values, and preventing non-plugin asset selection.</li>
<h3>Rider and Debugger Workflow Maturity</h3>
<li>Added Rider to IntelliJ debugger support coverage with dedicated Rider integration/debugger test flows.</li>
<li>Introduced RLVR-based Rider debugger prompt iteration: agents were trained in a virtual environment to test and refine prompts for reliable debugger support.</li>
<li>Added Rider IDE integration coverage for debugger workflows and introduced `RiderPlaygroundTest` for interactive debugging sessions.</li>
<li>Improved debugger prompts for event-driven suspension, idempotent breakpoints, and Rider/.NET expression handling.</li>
<li>Added run-test-at-caret prompt workflows and fixed action IDs/caret targeting in debugger demos.</li>
<li>Extracted shared debugger test helpers to reduce duplication between IntelliJ and Rider demo tests.</li>
<h3>Build & Infrastructure</h3>
<li>Extracted `intellij-downloader` and `kotlin-cli` modules and moved related tests into the new module boundaries.</li>
<li>Fixed IDE downloader platform resolution in containerized runs (correct archive per OS).</li>
<li>Improved integration-run stability via warm snapshot bootstrap hardening and test-suite parallelism controls.</li>
<li>Fixed ScriptExecutor timeout test behavior and excluded Docker CLI tests from the default fast suite.</li>
<p>Full release notes: <a href="https://mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com/releases/0.90.0/">mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com/releases/0.90.0/</a></p>]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>

