<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="com.jonnyzzz.mcp-steroid" url="https://github.com/jonnyzzz/mcp-steroid/releases/download/v0.92.0/mcp-steroid-0.92.0-59b78976.zip" version="0.92.0-59b78976">
    <idea-version since-build="253"/>
    <name>MCP Steroid</name>
    <vendor>jonnyzzz.com</vendor>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><b>MCP Steroid</b> brings the full power of the IntelliJ Platform to AI agents through the Model Context Protocol (MCP).</p>
<p>IntelliJ platform works for AI agents as great as for human developers.</p>
<ul>
<li><b>9 MCP Tools:</b> Control IntelliJ IDEA programmatically — execute code, take screenshots, discover actions, debug, and more</li>
<li><b>58 MCP Resources:</b> Comprehensive guides covering LSP, IDE operations, debugger, tests, VCS, and more</li>
<li><b>Vision Capabilities:</b> AI agents can see your IDE with screenshots and OCR</li>
<li><b>Deep Integration:</b> Access PSI, inspections, refactorings, and full IntelliJ Platform API</li>
<li><b>Human Oversight:</b> Review and approve code execution with configurable safety controls</li>
</ul>
<p>Compatible with all IntelliJ Platform-based IDEs: IntelliJ IDEA, PyCharm, WebStorm, GoLand, CLion, Rider, and more.</p>
<p>Requirements: IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 or newer (build 253 or later).</p>
<p>Visit <a href="https://mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com">mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com</a> for documentation and examples.</p>]]></description>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[<h2>What's New in v0.92.0</h2>
<h3>0.92.0</h3>
<p>### MCP Steroid Is Now Open Source and Supported by JetBrains</p>
<p>MCP Steroid is now licensed under **Apache 2.0** and officially supported by JetBrains. This release marks a milestone for the project — the full source is available for community contributions, audits, and forks. Read the full announcement: [MCP Steroid Goes Open Source](https://jonnyzzz.com/blog/2026/04/07/mcp-steroid-open-source/)</p>
<p>### Your IDE Skill Factory</p>
<p>MCP Steroid is more than a code-execution bridge — it is your **IDE Skill Factory**. Each prompt resource, each `steroid_execute_code` call, each debugging session is a scenario we collect and refine to make AI agents more capable in the IDE. We are actively gathering real-world workflows. Learn more and contribute yours: [MCP Steroid as Skill Factory](https://jonnyzzz.com/blog/2026/04/08/mcp-steroid-skill-factory/)</p>
<p>### Critical Bug Fix: Script Classpath (#16)</p>
<p>**Content module JARs were missing from the script compile classpath.** This caused compilation failures for code using classes from IDE content modules — including Kotlin plugin internals and Java API wrappers provided by bundled plugins. AI agents would receive `unresolved reference` errors even for APIs that are clearly available in the IDE.</p>
<p>The fix ensures that all JARs from loaded plugin classloaders are included when building the script classpath. ([#16](https://github.com/jonnyzzz/mcp-steroid/issues/16))</p>
<p>### Exact Error Locations in Your Code</p>
<p>When something goes wrong, agents now see exactly where — in **your code**, not in the internal wrapper.</p>
<li><b>Compiler errors</b> now report the line number in the user-supplied code block, not in the generated wrapper class. A syntax error on line 3 of your snippet is now reported as line 3, not line 47.</li>
<li><b>Runtime stack traces</b> are remapped the same way: exception frames pointing into MCP Steroid's wrapper code are translated to the original user-code line.</li>
<li><b>Framework and wrapper frames</b> are stripped from stack traces entirely, leaving only the frames that matter for diagnosis.</li>
<p>### Cleaner Tool Output</p>
<p>Per-call boilerplate messages — `FILE DISCOVERY`, `PRO Tip`, `TIP` — have been removed from every tool response. These static hints were repeating on every invocation and adding noise without value. Output is now focused on execution results.</p>
<p>### McpScriptContext Available as Prompt Resource</p>
<p>`McpScriptContext` — the object giving scripts access to the `project`, `disposable`, `println()`, `progress()`, and other IDE integration helpers — is now documented as a built-in MCP resource article. Agents can browse it via `mcp-steroid://skill/coding-with-intellij`.</p>
<p>### Update Notification Now Includes Download Link</p>
<p>When a newer version of the plugin is available, the in-IDE update notification now shows a direct download link, making it faster to grab the latest release without navigating to the website.</p>
<p>Full release notes: <a href="https://mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com/releases/0.92.0/">mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com/releases/0.92.0/</a></p>]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>

